

chintan.patel.47@gmail.com

+91-9099935498

0

Ahmedabad, India

in

in.linkedin.com/in/cansdeveloper

SKILLS

Drupal

CorePHP

Laravel

Codeigniter

Amazon Alexa

Google assistant

Node.js

Angular.js

python

Mysql

MongoDb

Postgresql

LANGUAGES

Gujarati











Chintan Patel

Programmer

9+ Years of experience in application development using LAMP stack and MEAN stack. Cloud server deployment & maintenance for AWS, Google cloud, Microsoft Azure. Create chatbot using google assistant actions and amazon alexa skill sets. I have always been interested in learning new technology and implement for best solution.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Analyst

Blueocean market intelligence Pvt. Ltd.

04/2016 - 05/2018

Mumbai,India

Responsibility

- Application development using Drupal ,Codeigniter and Laravel.
- Manage Cloud server of Google, AWS, Azure.
- Develop google actions using dialogflow for google home devices and develop alexa skills using AWS lamda & alexa skill set for amazon echo devices.

Team Lead of PHP

Codal Inc.

08/2014 - 10/2015

Ahmedabad,India

Responsibility

- Application development using Drupal ,Codeigniter and Laravel.
- Requirement understanding, time line and estimation.
- Task distribution, project management, meet the client deadlines, debugging and problem solving.

Team Lead of PHP and web design

Renus Technologix

10/2013 - 08/2014

PHP Programmer

Elegant Microweb technology Pvt. Ltd.

07/2012 – 05/2013 Ahmedabad,India

Web developer ACTuniv Group

03/2010 - 06/2012

Ahmedabad,India

ACHIEVEMENTS

Rookie Award at Blueocean market intelligence Pvt Ltd (08/2016)

Innovation and thought leadership award at Blueocean Market Intelligence (01/2017)

Socrates at Blueocean Market Intelligance Pvt ltd (06/2017)

EDUCATION

Bachelors of engineering

Goverment college of engineering

06/2004 – 06/2009 Patan,India